Guide to the George A. Lindbeck Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Collected Materials: Ecumenism, Series VIII
  - Lutheran-Catholic Dialogue
    - re: Church: "Ecumenism...Free Church Dilemma" by Robert G. Torbet, The Judson Press, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 895)
    - re: Church: "L'Eglise est-elle infaillible ou indefectible?" in Theologie, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 896)
    - re: Church: "Das Signal Unfehlbarkeit: Bischof Hermann Dietzfelbinger sprach uber 'Mysterium ecclesiae'", 1973 (Box 37, Folder 897)
    - re: Church: "Church Leadership Perspectives on the Implementation of Dialogue Proposals" by James R. Crumley, Jr. in Journal of Ecumenical Studies, v.23 n.3, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 898)
    - re: Commission: "Udienza del Papa alla commissione cattolico-luterana" in O.R., 1984 (Box 37, Folder 899)
    - re: Commission: "A Quarter Century of Lutheran-Roman Catholic Dialogue in the United States" by John Reumann, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 900)
    - re: Communion: "Lutheran-Reformed Team Proposes Full Communion" in A Common Calling, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 901)
    - re: Conversion: "'Conversion': A Biblical Study" by Jacob W. Heikkinen, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 902)
    - re: Council of Trent: "The Minister of the Eucharist According to the Council of Trent" by Harry J. McSorley; "The Lutheran Reformation and the Council of Trent on the Obligatory Character of the Confession of Sins: Doctrinal Precedents and Present Possibilities" by Carl J. Peter; "The Decree on Justification in the Council of Trent" by Carl J. Peter (Box 37, Folder 903)
    - re: Covenant: "Covenant Between the Diocese of Charlotte and the Diocese of Raleigh and the Synod of North Carolina", 1990 (Box 37, Folder 904)
    - re: Dialogue: :Lutherans Explore Catholicism" by Harold Butcher in St. Joseph Magazine, v.58, 1957 (Box 37, Folder 905)
    - re: Dialogue: "Christen im Dialog mit Menschen Anderen Glaubens", 1967 (Box 37, Folder 906)
    - re: Doctrine: "The Holy Trinity" by George W. Elderkin, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 907)
    - re: Doctrine: "Commission on the Comprehensive Study of the Doctrine of the Ministry: The Word of Creation and the Word of Redemption" by Walter J. Kukkonen, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 908)
    - re: Doctrine: "How is Man Saved?: Catholic, Lutheran Theologians Unsnarl Doctrinal Knot" by Jerry Filteau in Florida Catholic, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 909)
    - re: Dogma: "Dogma as an Ecumenical Problem" by Avery Dulles in Theological Studies, nd (Box 37, Folder 910)
    - re: Councils: "Someone Does Care"; "In Thy Light", nd (Box 37, Folder 911)
    - re: Discussion: "On the Theology of Ecumenical Discussion", nd (Box 37, Folder 912)
    - re: Ecumenism: "Le Mouvement Oecumenique" by Charle Boyer, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 913)
    - re: Ecumenism: "Ecumenism Against Itself" by Richard J. Neuhaus, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 914)
    - re: Ecumenism: "Grass Roots Ecumenism", nd (Box 37, Folder 915)
    - re: Episcopacy: "Comments on Professor Lindbeck's Reply" by Arthur Carl Piepkorn, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 916)
    - re: Episcopacy: "Task Force Discusses Episcopate, Orders, with Bilateral Dialogue Representatives" in Study of Ministry Report, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 917)
    - re: Eschatology: "The Eschatology of Lumen Gentium: Beyond in Both Directions" by Carl J. Peter (Box 37, Folder 918)
    - re: Faith: "Response to Robert Jenson at 'A Call to Faithfulness'" by James M. Kittelson, nd (Box 37, Folder 919)
    - re: Germany: "Katholiken und Protestanten in Deutschland: Ein Gesprach mit Professor Gerhard Schmidtchen" (Box 37, Folder 920)
    - re: Hartford Affirmation: "Neuhaus, Coffin, Cox: SRO at 475" in Christian Century, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 921)
    - re: Infallibility: "L'Infaillibilite de l'Eglise du point de vue d'un theologien orthodoxe" by R. P. Nicolas Afanassieff in Journees oecumeniques de Chevetogne, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 922)
    - re: Infallibility: "Autorite du Magistere et vie de foi ecclesiale" in Nouvelle Revue Theologique, n.4, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 923)
    - re: Infallibility: "Infallibility Beyond Polemics" by Gregory Baum in Commonweal, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 924)
    - re: Infallibility: "Im Interesse der Sache" by Hans Kung in Stimmem der Zeit; "Kritik an Hans Kung" by Karl Rahner in Stimmen der Zeit, 1971; 1970 (Box 37, Folder 925)
    - re: Infallibility: "Papal Infallibility: The Remaining Agenda" by Philip S. Kaufman in Origins, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 926)
    - re: Infallibility: "Propositioni Fallibili Assensus Fidei Christianae Jure Divino Requisitus?" by Carl J. Peter, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 927)
    - re: Infallibility: "Papal Infallibility, 1350-1600" by Jared Wicke, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 928)
    - re: Infallibility: "Infallibility: The Crossroads of Doctrine" by Peter Chirico, Sheed Andrews and McMeel, Inc. (part 1), 1976 (Box 37, Folder 929)
    - re: Infallibility: "Infallibility: The Crossroads of Doctrine" by Peter Chirico, Sheed Andrews and McMeel, Inc. (part 2), 1976 (Box 37, Folder 930)
    - re: Infallibility: "Infallibility: The Crossroads of Doctrine" by Peter Chirico, Sheed Andrews and McMeel, Inc. (part 3), 1976 (Box 38, Folder 931)
    - re: Infallibility: "Infallibility: The Crossroads of Doctrine" by Peter Chirico, Sheed Andrews and McMeel, Inc. (part 4), 1976 (Box 38, Folder 932)
    - re: Infallibility: "Infallibility: A Structural Analysis" by Tavard, nd (Box 38, Folder 933)
    - re: Infallibility: "Irren ist menschlich: zur Kontroverse um Hans Kung Buch 'Unfehlbar? Eine Anfrage'" by Eberhard Jungel in Katholizismus, nd (Box 38, Folder 934)
    - re: Infallibility: "The Office of Teaching in the Christian Church According to the Ne w Testament" by Joseph A. Fitzmeyer, nd (Box 38, Folder 935)
    - re: Infallibility: "Papal Infallibility and the Marian Definitions, Some Considerations" by Eamon R. Carroll (Box 38, Folder 936)
    - re: Infallibility: "Remarks on Brian Tierney's Book, Origins of Papal Infallibility " by K. Froehlich, nd (Box 38, Folder 93 7)
    - re: Infallibility: "Scriptural Loci on Infallibility", nd (Box 38, Folder 938)
    - re: Intercommunion: "The Conditions for an Acceptable Intercommunion" by Jean-Jacques von Alimen in Concilium, v.44, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 939)
    - re: Intercommunion: "Reciprocal Admission to the Lord's Supper", nd (Box 38, Folder 940)
    - re: Justification by Faith: "La doctrine de la justification dans le dialogue interconfessionel mene par l'Eglise lutherienne" by Harding Meyer in Revue d'Histoire et de Philosophie Religieuses, n.1; "Simul iustus et peccator in Augustine, Aquinas, and Luther: Toward Putting the Debate in Context" by James F. McCue in Princeton; "Some Observations on the Doctrine of Justification in the Roman Catholic Tradition" by James F. McCue in Princeton; "The Doctrine of Justification in the Lutheran Dialogue with Other Churches" by Meyer in One in Christ: A Catholic Ecumenical Review, v. XVII n.2, 1977; 1979; 1979; 1981 (Box 38, Folder 941)
    - re: Justification by Faith: "U.S. Lutheran-Roman Catholic Dialogue: Justification by Faith", 1985 (Box 38, Folder 942)
    - re: Justification by Faith: "Lutheran Church in America Response to Lutheran-Roman Catholic Dialogue Report on Justification", 1986 (Box 38, Folder 943)
    - re: Justification by Faith: "A Statement of Response of the Inter-Church Relations Committee of the American Lutheran Church to the Lutheran/Roman Catholic Dialogue on Justification", 1986 (Box 38, Folder 944)
    - re: Justification by Faith: "Justification and the Catholic Principle Revisited" by Carl J. Peter; "Brief Remarks on Luther's Interpretation of Pauline Justification" by Joseph A. Fitzmeyer; "Changing Soteriology in Ecumenical Context" by Joseph A. Burgess (Box 38, Folder 945)
    - re: Konfession: untitled, nd (Box 38, Folder 946)
    - re: Lindbeck's Trip to South America, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 947)
    - re: Luther: "Luthers okumenische Bedeutung heute" by Hans L. Martensen in Lutherische Monatshefte, v. VI; "Luther's Theology: A Modern Catholic Reflection" by Avery Dulles; "Gemeinsames romisch-katholisches/evangelisch-lutherisches Wort zu Martin Luther", 1967; 1980; nd (Box 38, Folder 948)
    - re: Mary/Saints: "Luther's Mariology: An Assessment Based on Luther's Translations and Expositions of Luke 1:26-55" by Thomas Worcester; "Luther and the Veneration of Mary" by Eric W. Gritsch; "Mary" by John Reumann in Encyclopedia of Religion, 1982; 1984; 1984 (Box 38, Folder 949)
    - re: Mary/Saints: "Mary in the Hymns of Martin Luther" by Karlfried Froehlich; "Karl Rahner on the Mediation of the Saints" by Avery Dulles; "Mary and the Saints in Contemporary Lutheran Worship: An Overview" by John F. Johnson, nd; nd; 1985 (Box 38, Folder 950)
    - re: Mediation: "The Critical Issue: The One Mediator and Questions About Mediation" (Box 38, Folder 951)
    - re: Ministry: "Ecumenical Agreement on Ministry", 1972 (Box 38, Folder 952)
    - Ministry: "The Powerlessness of God: Sacramental Ministry to Survivors of Abuse" by Rebecca Frey in Advent, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 953)
    - re: Ministry: "Eucharist and Ministry" (Box 38, Folder 954)
    - re: Ministry: "Public Ministry and its Limits" by Gerhard O. Forde (Box 39, Folder 955)
    - re: Papal Primacy: "Papal Primacy" in New York Times; "The Papacy and Christian Symbolism", 1974; nd (Box 39, Folder 957)
    - re: Petrine Office: "What is the Petrine Function?" by George H. Tavard; "The Petrine Office: Some Ecumenical Projections" by Baker, nd (Box 39, Folder 958)
    - re: Project Open House: "Project Open House", 1966 (Box 39, Folder 959)
    - re: Prophecy: "Is Prophecy a Jigsaw Puzzle?" in Christianity Today, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 960)
    - re: Ratzinger: "Ratzinger, the Ecumenical Prefect" in 30 Days, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 961)
    - re: Salvation: "The Free Gift of Salvation" in Spirit and Forms of Protestantism (Box 39, Folder 962)
    - re: Sanction: "La Sanction Prise Contre Mgr Lefebvre" in Le Monde, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 963)
    - re: Teaching Authority: "Teaching Authority of Vatican II" in Ecumenist, v.3 n.6; "The Right of Catholics to Dissent from 'Humanae Vitae'" in Ecumenist, 1965; 1969 (Box 39, Folder 964)
    - re: Totalitarianism: "Totalitarisme et contre-totalitarisme" in Le Monde, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 965)
    - re: Unity: :The Growing Unity" by John Knox in The Early Church and the Coming Great Church, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 966)
    - re: Unity: "Church Unity is a Growing Thing" by F. Gerald Ensley in Christian Century, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 967)
    - re: Unity: "Response, Demur" by Carl E. Braaten in Christian Century, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 968)
    - re: Unity: "Unity: A Wide Door and Many Adversaries" by Patrick C. Rodger in Ecumenical Review, vol. XVIII n .2, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 969)
    - re: Unity: "Fraternity is Not What Christ Asked of Church" by Frank Morriss in St. Loius Review, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 970)
    - re: Unity: "Yale's Lindbeck Sees Path to Unity Hopeful" by Miriam Devine in The Catholic Transcript, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 971)
    - re: Unity: "Quodlibetum on the Church's Treasures (Thesauri Ecclesiae)" Carl J. Peter, nd (Box 39, Folder 972)
    - re: Worship: "Northwest Catholics, Lutherans Celebrate at Reformation Festival Worship Service" by Gloria Thiele and Cindy Wooden in The Progress, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 973)
    - Miscellaneous Newspaper Articles, nd (Box 39, Folder 974)
    - Re. Lutheran- Roman Catholic dialogue, 1975, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 22)
    - Presentation by Joseph Cardinal Bernardin, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 23)
    - Presentation by Edward Idris Cardinal Cassidy, 2000 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - American Lutheran-Catholic Dialogue
    - Semi-annual Series: #6-New York City, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 975)
    - Semi-annual Series: #7-Williamsburg, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 976)
    - 6th Session of LWF and Catholic Bishops, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 977)
    - Semi-annual Series: #8-San Francisco, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 978)
    - Semi-annual Series: #9: The Use of Church as Applied ot Protestant Denominations in the Documents of Vatican II, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 979)
    - Semi-annual Series: #12-Miami, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 980)
    - Semi-annual Series: #14-Greenwich, CT, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 981)
    - Patristics Panel Materials-St. Louis, MO, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 982)
    - Panel on Peter in the New Testament, 1971-72 (Box 39, Folder 983)
    - Semi-annual Series: #15-New Orleans, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 984)
    - Semi-annual Series: #16-Minneapolis, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 985)
    - Semi-annual Series: #17-San Antonio, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 986)
    - Colloquim on Ecumenical Dialogue-Minneapolis, MN, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 987)
    - Papers (incl. "Unity and Christian Responsibility"; "The Theology of Liberation and the Structures of the Church"; "Ministry and the Church Universal: Differing Attitudes Towards Papal Primacy"), 1973-74 (Box 40, Folder 988)
    - Lutheran-Roman Catholic Consultation-Marriotsville, MD, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 989)
    - 21st Meeting of the Dialogue Group: Minutes-Princeton, NJ, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 990)
    - Meeting of Dialogue Group: Minutes-St. Louis, MO, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 991)
    - Administrative Meeting-Washington, D.C., 1975 (Box 40, Folder 992)
    - Meeting of Dialogue Group: Minutes-Washington, D.C., 1975 (Box 40, Folder 993)
    - Papers (incl. "What Does it Mean for a Christian to Say 'Christ is the Truth'?" by Joseph A. Burgess; "Summary of Notes on the PE", 1975 (Box 40, Folder 994)
    - Semi-Annual Series #24-Scottsdale, AZ, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 995)
    - Meeting of Dialogue Group: Minutes-Washington, D.C., 1977 (Box 40, Folder 996)
    - Lutheran Presidents/Catholic Bishops Meeting-Washington, D.C., 1977 (Box 40, Folder 997)
    - Lutheran Presidents/Catholic Bishops Meeting-Columbia, SC, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 998)
    - Lutheran Presidents/Catholic Bishops Materials-Washington, D.C., 1978 (Box 40, Folder 999)
    - Lutheran Presidents/Catholic Bishops Meeting: Minutes-Washington, D.C., 1978 (Box 40, Folder 1000)
    - Lutheran Presidents/Catholic Bishops Meeting: Minutes-New York, NY, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 1001)
    - Sacred Congregation for the Doctrine of Faith Materials, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 1002)
    - Roman Catholic and Lutheran Bishops Meeting: Minutes-Washington, D.C., 1980 (Box 40, Folder 1003)
    - Proposed Draft of Letter Regarding Sacred Congregation for the Doctrine of Faith, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 1004)
    - Roman Catholic and Lutheran Bishops Meeting: Minutes-Washington, D.C., 1981 (Box 41, Folder 1005)
    - Meeting of Dialogue Group: Information, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 1006)
    - Meeting of Dialogue Group: Information-San Antonio, TX, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 1007)
    - Committee on Doctrine (COD) Critique of Dialogues, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 1008)
    - Committee on Doctrine (COD) Critique of Dialogues, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 1009)
    - Semi-Annual Series #40, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 1010)
    - Semi-Annual Series #41-Techny, IL, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 1011)
    - Meeting of Dialogue Group: Minutes, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 1012)
    - Lutheran Presidents/Catholic Bishops Meeting: Materials-Washington D.C., 1985 (Box 41, Folder 1013)
    - Meeting of Dialogue Group: Minutes, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 1014)
    - Semi-Annual Series-Burlingame, CA, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 1015)
    - Catholic Responses to Dialogue Questions, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 1016)
    - Meeting of Dialogue Group: Writing-Area Groups, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 1017)
    - Semi-Annual Series #43-Wheeling, WV; #44-Tampa, FL, 1986; 1987 (Box 41, Folder 1018)
    - Semi-Annual Series Drafting Committee Report-One Mediator, the Saints, and Mary, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 1019)
    - Semi-Annual Series: Minutes, nd (Box 41, Folder 1020)
    - Meeting of Dialogue Group: Several Theses, nd (Box 41, Folder 1021)
    - Miscellaneous Papers (incl. untitled by Robert Eno), nd (Box 41, Folder 1022)
    - Dialogue Group: Roster of Participants, nd (Box 41, Folder 1023)
  - International Lutheran-Roman Catholic Dialogue
    - Papers (incl. "Das Kirchlicher Lehramt nach Lutherischer und Katholischer Auffassung"), 1963 (Box 41, Folder 1024)
    - Latin American Consultation and Related Documents, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 1025)
    - Eucharist and Ministry (ITC Report), 1971 (Box 41, Folder 1026)
    - Institute for Ecumenical Research (IER)-Consultation Bilateral Conversations-Geneva, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 1027)
    - Institute for Ecumenical Research (IER): "The First Phase of the Activities of the Institute for Ecumenical Studies", 1964 (Box 41, Folder 1028)
    - Institute for Ecumenical Research (IER): "Eucharistic Hospitality", 1973 (Box 42, Folder 1029)
    - Institute for Ecumenical Research (IER): "A Decade of Ecumenical Achievement", 1974 (Box 42, Folder 1030)
    - "Kommission fur Glauben end Kirchenverfassung", 1974 (Box 42, Folder 1031)
    - Discussion Group Report: "Marriage, Family, and the Christian Faith"-Sweden, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1032)
    - Institute for Ecumenical Research (IER): "Lutherisch Einheit", 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1033)
    - Institute for Ecumenical Research (IER): Joint Commission Working Group Information, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1034)
    - Sacred Congregation for the Doctrine of Faith: "Commentary on the Declaration of the Sacred Congregation for the Doctrine of the Faith on the Question of the Admission of Women to the Ministerial Priesthood", 1976 (Box 42, Folder 1035)
    - "Einleitung", 1978 (Box 42, Folder 1036)
    - Institute for Ecumenical Research (IER): "An die Mitglieder des Unterausschusses uber das Amt", 1978 (Box 42, Folder 1037)
    - "Die 'ein fur alle Mal' geschehene Heilstat Gottes in Jesus Christus", 1979 (Box 42, Folder 1038)
    - Institute for Ecumenical Research (IER): "Recognition of CA", 1979 (Box 42, Folder 1039)
    - Institute for Ecumenical Research (IER): "Besprechung uber das Amtspapier", 1980 (Box 42, Folder 1040)
    - Dialogue Group: Papers (incl. "Lagebericht der Theologischen Gesprachsgruppe Schweden"), 1981 (Box 42, Folder 1041)
    - Institute for Ecumenical Research (IER): "Dokument uber das geistliche Amt in der Kirche", 1981 (Box 42, Folder 1042)
    - 2nd Round Dialogue: "Pope Addresses Catholic-Lutheran Dialogue as it Ends 2nd Round", 1984 (Box 42, Folder 1043)
    - Institute for Ecumenical Research (IER): "Sketch of a Problem to Be Investigated by the Strassbourg Institute for Ecumenical Research", 1985 (Box 42, Folder 1044)
    - Department of Studies-Lutheran World Federation: "Am Ende der zweiten Phase des Dialogs zwischen romischen Katholischer Kirche und Lutherischem Weltbund" by Harding Meyer, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 1045)
    - Dialogue Group: Papers (incl. "The Early Christian Church and its Significance" by Adolf Martin Ritter) (Box 42, Folder 1046)
  - Joint Theological Commission
    - Study Documents: "Catholicity and Apostolicity; Reports"; "Apostolicity: The Present Position of Studies" by R. Schnackenburg; "Pluralism and Unity: The Possibility of a Variety of Typologies with the Same Ecclesial Allegiance" by Emmanuel Lanne, 1967-68 (Box 42, Folder 1047)
    - Study Documents: "Report of the Joint Lutheran/Roman Catholic Study Commission on the Gospel and the Church", 1972 (Box 42, Folder 1048)
    - Gemeinsame Romisch-katholisch/Lutherische Arbeitsgruppe: Protokoll, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 1049)
    - Gemeinsame Romisch-katholisch/Lutherische Arbeitsgrouppe: Agenda, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 1050)
    - 1st Session of Joint Commission: "Reflexions nur les dialogues theologiques interconfessionnels"-Geneva, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 1051)
    - 2nd Session of Joint Commission: Minutes-Rome, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 1052)
    - 3rd Session of Joint Commission: Report-Strassburg, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 1053)
    - 3rd Session of Joint Commission: Documentation-Strassburg, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 1054)
    - 3rd Session of Joint Commission: Materials-Strassburg, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 1055)
    - 4th Session of Joint Commission: Report-Paderborn, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 1056)
    - 4th Session of Joint Commission: Documentation-Paderborn, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 1057)
    - Joint Commission: "Das geistliche Amt"-Hamburg, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 1058)
    - Dialogue Group: Protocol, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 1059)
    - Dialogue Group: Materials, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 1060)
    - 5th Session of Joint Commission: Report-Sweden, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 1061)
    - 5th Session of Joint Commission: Agenda-Sweden, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 1062)
    - Dialogue Group: Materials, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 1063)
    - 6th Session of Joint Commission: Report-Augsburg, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 1064)
    - 6th Session of Joint Commission: Documentation-Augsburg, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 1065)
    - Papers: "Ways to Community"-Augsburg, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 1066)
    - Papers: "Das geistliche Amt"-Augsburg, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 1067)
    - Papers: "Wege zur Gemeinschaft", 1980 (Box 43, Folder 1068)
    - 7th Session of Joint Commission: Report-Lantana, FL, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 1069)
    - 7th Session of Joint Commission: Agenda-Lantana, FL, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 1070)
    - 500th Anniversary of Martin Luther's Birth Meeting-Kopenhagen/Alingsas, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 1071)
    - 8th Session of Joint Commission: Report-Venice, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 1072)
    - 8th Session of Joint Commission: Agenda-Venice, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 1073)
    - 9th Session of Joint Commission: Report-Kloster Kirchberg, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 1074)
    - 9th Session of Joint Commission: Agenda-Kloster Kirchberg, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 1075)
    - 9th Session of Joint Commission: Agenda-Kloster Kirchberg, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 1076)
    - Papers: "Modelle und Formen der Einigung" (Box 44, Folder 1077)
    - Papers: "Reciprocal Admission to the Eucharist", nd (Box 44, Folder 1078)
    - 10th Session of Joint Commission: Report-Rome, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 1079)
    - Papers: Notes on Reciprocal Admission, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 1080)
    - 10th Session of Joint Commission: Agenda-Rome, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 1081)
    - Papers: "Das Problem des Amtes in heutiger lutherisch/katholischer Begegnung" by Vinzenz Pfnur, nd (Box 44, Folder 1082)
    - Papers: "The Future Work of the Joint Roman Catholic/Lutheran Commission", 1985 (Box 44, Folder 1083)
    - Papers: "Einheit vor Uns", 1985 (Box 44, Folder 1084)
    - Papers: "Facing Towards Unity: Models, Forms and Phases of Catholic-Lutheran Church Fellowship", 1985 (Box 44, Folder 1085)
    - Joint Commission Meetings: List of Dates, 1973-84 (Box 44, Folder 1086)
    - Papers: "Das geistliche Amt in der Kirche" (Box 44, Folder 1087)
    - Papers: "Die Zulassung der Frauen zum Amt", nd (Box 44, Folder 1088)
    - Joint Commission Meetings: Participation List and Notes (Box 44, Folder 1089)
  - Roman Catholic
    - General
      - re: Apostolic Succession: "Apostolic Succession: A Clarification" in Origins, v.4 n.13, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 1090)
      - re: Church: ""Redemptoris Missio" in International Bulletin of Missionary Research, v.15 n.2; "Redemptoris Mission: The Ecumenical Context" by George Lindbeck (unpublished), 1991; 1991 (Box 44, Folder 1091)
      - re: Church: "The Change That No One Noticed" by R.G. Peters in Catholic Digest; "What Would You Like to Know About the Church?" by Kenneth Ryan in Catholic Digest, nd; 1977 (Box 44, Folder 1092)
      - re: Church: "Irrtumer uber die Kirche?: Eine Dokumentation zur Erklarung der Glaubenskongregation vom 5. Juli" in Dokumentation (Box 44, Folder 1093)
      - re: Confession: "Signification des confessions de foi" by J.P. Jossua in Problemes de l'Ecumenisme (Box 44, Folder 1094)
      - re: Divine Law: "Dimensione of Jus Divinum in Roman Catholic Theology" by Carl J. Peter, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 1095)
      - re: Doctrine: "Declaratio Circa Catholicam Doctrinam de Ecclesia Contra Nonnullos Errores Hodiernos Tuendam" by Sacra Congregatio pro Doctrina Fidei (Box 44, Folder 1096)